Guide to the National Council of American Soviet Friendship Records TAM.134
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Activities, Programs, Special Projects, 1943-1990
  - Subseries II:A: NCASF Activities (1943-1989)
    - Rally For Peace, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - World Peace Delegation, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - "From Bombs and Death to Cooperation and Peace Symposium, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Educational Conference of NCASF, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - "Facts, not Fiction--the Soviet Union Today" 1951 Lecture Series (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Stalingrad Victory Luncheon, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Symposium on Germany, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Rally For Peace--Rockland Palace, NY, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Women's Exposition for Peace and Freedom, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Stalingrad Meeting, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Stalin Memorial Meeting, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Tenth Anniversary Exhibit, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - "USA/USSR Cooperation for Peace", 1953 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Rally for Peace, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Rally for Peace, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Meeting on Peaceful Coexistence, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Melish/Goshal Forum, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Rally for Peace and Friendship, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Annual Spring Bazaars, 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Morford Testimonial, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Morford Testimonial--Correspondence, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Anna Louise Strong Meeting, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Anna Louise Strong Reception, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Morford Picnic, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Annual Rally, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - General Yakhontoff Tour, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Rockwell Kent Dinner, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Peace Campaign, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Epstein Reports on Soviet Union, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Annual Rally, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Photo Exhibit, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Mr and Mrs RW France Reception, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Scott Nearing Lecture, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Moiseyev Folk Dancers, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Kumar Goshal Lecture, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Ashkenazy Piano Recital, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Beryozka Dancers, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Annual Rally, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Annual Rallies for Peace and Friendship, 1958-1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Peace Stamps Campaign, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Two Concerts, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Rockwell Kent Meeting, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Bolshoi Ballet, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Theodore Bayer Memorial, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Russian Music and Dance Festival, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Annual Rally, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Moscow State Symphony, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Welcome home Luncheon for Morfords, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Peace Stamps Campaign, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Committee to Greet the 15th UN General Assembly, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Sviatoslav Richter Concerts, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Annual Rally, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Forum on Invasion of Cuba, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Annual Rally, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Annual Rally, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - NCASF 20th Anniversary Dinner, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Harry Ward 90th Birthday Party, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Annual Rally, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - US Tour Guide Arrested in USSR, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Annual Rally, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Moscow Art Theater, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Moiseyev Folk Dancers, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Annual Rally, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Brochure, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Testimonial, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Sponsors, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Biographies of Speakers, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Messages, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Thank You Letters 1965 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Committee Minutes 1965 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Publicity, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Morford Correspondence, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--General Correspondence, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Morford 20th Anniversary--Other Cities, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Annual Rally, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Essay Contest, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Annual Rally, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Annual Rally, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 60.1)
    - American-Soviet Print Show, Moscow, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Annual Rally, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Societies for Friendship with the Soviet Union, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Symposium on Lenin, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Reception for Elizabeth Moos, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Celebration of the Life of Rockwell Kent, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Annual Rally, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Annual Rally, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Salute to Paul Robeson--75th Birthday, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - 70 and 30 Luncheon, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - City-as-School Program, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Annual Rally, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Annual Rally, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Dance Programs, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Trade Unions--Baker Amendment, 1983-1989 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - 12th World Festival of Youth and Students, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - 12th World Festival of Youth and Students--Applications, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Childrens' Art Exchange, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Gospel Concert, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Second US-Soviet Youth Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - "Amerika" Protest, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Third US-Soviet Youth Conference, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Chernobyl Fire Chief Address, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Penpal Letters--East Sparta Elementary School, East Sparta Ohio, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - John Reed Centenary, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Tribute to John Randolph, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Veatch Program--Grant Application, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 86.1)
    - Nani Bregvatze Performances, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Theodore Bayer Memorial Fund, undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - WBAI Conference -- "Against Our Will", October 21, 1975
      Scope and Contents
      Content Warning: These recordings contain explicit content about violence against women.
      - Tape #1, 12-1AM, cuid44624 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A4)
        Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
        Duration: 63 min
      - Tape #2, 1-2AM, cuid44623 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A3)
        Duration: 62 min
      - Tape #3, 2-3AM, cuid44622 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A2)
      - Tape #4, 3-4AM, cuid44621 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A1)
        Duration: 56 minutes
    - Yolanda Bako/Ch. 2, Eye-On, October 18, 1975; cuid44625 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A5)
      Content Warning: This recording contains explicit content about violence against women.
      Duration: 30 min
    - WBAI Conference -- Rape Conference, Part 4, October 12, 1975; cuid44626 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A6)
      Duration: 53 min
    - M & D Conference - Betty Berry Workshop 1/20/74, 20 January 1974 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A7)
    - WBAI Conference -- Rape Conference, September 20-27, 1975
      - Part 1, September 20, 1975; cuid44627 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A8)
        Duration: 58 min
      - Part 2, September 27, 1975; cuid44628 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A9)
        Duration: 64 min
    - WBAI Conference -- Rape Program, March 26, 1975
      - Part 1, 4-5PM, cuid44629 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A10)
      - Part 2, 5-6PM, cuid44630 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A11)
    - M & D Conference - Betty Berry Workshop 1/19/74, 19 January 1974 (Box 18, Cassette 44.A12)
    - Morford Banquet - 1/26/66, 26 January 1966 (Box 18, Reel 44.A13-44.A15)
    - WBAI Conference - 9/20/75 Rape Conf. Pt. 1, 20 September 1975 (Box 18, Reel 44.A16)
    - WBAI Conference - 9/27/75 Rape Conf. Pt. 2, 27 September 1975 (Box 18, Reel 44.A17)
    - WBAI Conference - 3/26/75 Pt. 1, 26 March 1975 (Box 18, Reel 44.A18)
    - WBAI Conference - 3/26/75 Pt. 2, 26 March 1975 (Box 18, Reel 44.A19)
  - Subseries II:B: Exchange and Travel Programs (1950-1990)
    - "Russia with our Own Eyes"--Tour Report, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Exchange Programs USA/USSR, 1950-1956 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Visits to USSR--Individuals, 1955-1971 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Youth Exchanges and Conferences, 1956-1974 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Adult Travel Programs to the USSR, 1959-1984 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - USSR Delegation, 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Student Tours of the USSR, 1961-1978 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Goodwill Delegation, 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Goodwill Delegation, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Goodwill Delegation--Fort Worth, TX, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Goodwill Delegations--Itineraries, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Goodwill Delegation--Itinerary, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - USSR Friendship Tour--African-American Delegation Report, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Anniversary Tours, 1972-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Antioch College Exchange, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Sputnik International Youth Tourist Bureau, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Intourist Programs, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Artek--Orientation Materials, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Artek Delegation, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Artek--Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Artek--Mailing Lists, 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Artek--Leaders' Report, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Artek--Applications, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Artek--Applications, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Artek--Delegation, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Artek--Forms, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Artek--Leadership Applications, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Artek--Delegation, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Artek--News Releases, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Artek--Reunion Tour, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Artek--Applications, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Artek--Delegation, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Artek--Applications and Correspondence, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Artek--Applications: Not Accepted, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Artek--Correspondence, Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Artek--Delegation, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Artek--Applications: Not Accepted, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Artek--US Exhibit Guest Book, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Artek--General Information, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Artek--Leadership Applications, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Artek--Delegation, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Artek--Applications: Not Accepted, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Artek--General Information, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Artek--Articles, Pamphlets, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Artek--Correspondence with Delegates, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Artek--Delegation, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Artek--Disturbances, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Artek--Leadership Applications, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Artek--Applications: Not Accepted, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Artek--Correspondence, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Artek--Documentary Proposal, Orientation, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - US-USSR Exchange Delegations: Evaluations, 1980-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Pushkin Institute--Materials, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Pushkin Institute--Applications, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Pushkin Institute--Applications, 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Pushkin Institute--Applications, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Pushkin Institute--Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Friendship Travel--Programs, Itineraries, Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Friendship Travel--Programs, Itineraries, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Soviet Delegate--Article for Pravda, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Soviet Southern Tour, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Summer Camp Proposal, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Volga Peace Cruise, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Subseries II:C: Campaign for a Peoples' Peace Treaty/Peoples' Appeal for Peace (CPPT/PAP)
    - Peoples' Peace Treaty: Sister Cities Program, 1982-1989 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - PAP: Proposals, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - CPPT: Endorsements, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - CPPT: Outreach, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - CPPT: Minutes, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Peoples' Summit--April 8, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - CPPT: Inauguration, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Draft for a Peoples' Peace Treaty, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - PAP: Requests for Information, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - PAP: Pairing Requests--Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - CPPT-PAP: Fundraising, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - CPPT-PAP: Newsclippings, Publications, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Soviet Peace Committee/CPPT, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - CPPT-PAP: Internal Correspondence, Organizers Manual, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - PAP: Delegations, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Diocese of Dallas: Letters to Soviet Citizens, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - CPPT/PAP: Letters Accompanying Petitions, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - CPPT/PAP: Presentation of Petitions, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - CPPT/PAP: Updates, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - CPPT/PAP; Requests for Pairing, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - CPPT/PAP; Pairing Project--General, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - CPPT/PAP; History, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - CPPT/PAP; Mailing List, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - CPPT/PAP; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Subseries II:D: Other Organizations, Individuals, Concerned with American-Soviet Relations (1944-1989)
    - Adams, David, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - American Association for the Advancement of of Slavic Studies/Teachers of Russian, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - American Committee on US-Soviet Relations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - American-Russian Institute--Outline for Book, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - American-Soviet Relations--Other Organizations--General, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - American-Soviet Walk, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - American-Soviet Youth Forum, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Arts, Sciences, and Professions, National Council of, 1948-1955 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Canadian-Soviet Friendship, National Council of, 1944-1973 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Christians Associated for Relations with Eastern Europe, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Citizen Diplomacy, Inc., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Fine Line Productions (J. Woodruff), undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Kids Meeting Kids, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Peace Conference Ad Hoc Committee/World Council for Peace, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Peace Fleece, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Promoting Enduring Peace, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Research Program on the USSR, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Soviet-American Sail, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Soviet Peace Committee, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - UN Special Session on Disarmament--Meetings, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Women for a Meaningful Summit, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Women's International Democratic Federation, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - World Congress Devoted to the International 1986 Year of Peace, Copenhagen (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - YMCA Program, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Youth Revival for Survival, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Series III: NCASF Scrapbooks, 1942-1950
  Series III: NCASF Scrapbooks, consists of nine scrapbooks: 1. (NCASF) Committee of Women, 1944-1945; 2. Clippings re NCASF, November, 1944; 3. Rev. Dr. Hewitt Johnson, Dean of Canterbury, clippings re US visit, November-December, 1945; 4. Clippings on Soviet peace activities and statements, April-June, 1946, January-February, 1947; 5. Conference of the Committee of Women of the NCASF, November 16, 1944; 6. Denver, Colorado NCASF, 1943-1944; 7. Untitled, Soviet peace and cultural activities, 1949-1950; 8. Testimonial Album from American Industry to Soviet Industry (n.d., Russian War Relief, New York) 9. Clippings re NCASF activities, October-November, 1942.
  - Subseries III:A: Numbered Scrapbooks
    - Oct-Nov 1942 (Box 10, Folder Sb1)
    - Nov 1942: typed reports, newspaper clippings (including photos clips) (Box 10, Folder Sb2)
    - 1943-1944 Denver, Colorado (Box 11, Folder Sb3)
    - 16 Nov 1944: Conference of the Committee of Women of the NCASF (Box 11, Folder Sb4)
    - Nov 1944 Clippings (Box 11, Folder Sb5)
    - Committee of Women - Press Committee. Mid 1944 - Beginning 1945, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder Sb6)
    - Rev. Dr. Hewett Johnson, Dean of Canterbury, Nov-Dec 1945 (Box 12, Folder Sb7)
    - Apr, May, Jun 1946; Jan, Feb 1947, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder Sb8)
  - Subseries III:B: Un-numbered Scrapbooks
    - National Director Field Memos, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Testimonial Album from American Industry to Soviet Industry / Sponsored by Russian War Relief, Inc. [1943]., circa 1943 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Untitled: Clippings, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Photographs and Graphic Material, circa 1940-1989
  Series IV: Photographs and Graphic Material (circa 1940-1989) includes two disassembled scrapbooks from the early 1940s both titled "Pictures and stories of Soviet women in the War," photographs and memorabilia from a 1951 trip to the Soviet Union, and photographs from the Council's events and activities in the 1980s. This series also includes several mounted reproductions of woodcuts and other forms of art by Soviet artists, perhaps for an exhibit produced for or by the National Council of American-Soviet Friendship.
  - Conference Photographs, circa 1940-1949 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - "Pictures and Stories of Soviet Women in the War" Album 1 (I), 1942 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Pictures and Stories of Soviet Women in the War" Album 1 (II), 1942 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "Pictures and Stories of Soviet Women in the War" Album 2 (I), circa 1942 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Pictures and Stories of Soviet Women in the War" Album 2 (II), circa 1942 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - NCASF Recruitment Poster, circa 1947-1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Moscow Postcards, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Panoramic Photograph: George Washington's Birthday, Red Army Day Anniversary, National Council of American Soviet Friendship, The Waldorf Astoria, New York City, Feb 22, 1945 (Box Shared Tamiment XOS003, Folder 1)
  - Photographs from Soviet Union Trip, circa 1951 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - American Russian Institute Invitation to Peace, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Camp Artek, circa 1970-1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Hang 'Em Up - Peace, circa 1975-1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Madison, WI Chapter Photograph Album, Dec 1984-Jan 1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Campaign for a People's Peace Treaty, circa 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Martin Luther King Tribute, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit Photographs, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Tribute to John Randolph, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Event Photographs and Portraits, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Photographs from Life Magazine, undated (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS004, Folder 1)
  - Reproductions of Graphics by Soviet Artists, undated (Box 17)
  - Accession NPA 2000.228 photographs and booklet, 1943-1946 (Box 19, Box Shared Tamiment 011, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit: 25th anniversary of the USSR-USA Society, undated (Box 20, Folder 3-9)
  - David Curl photos, 1968, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Elvira Eastman photographs, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photo exhibit - Chernobyl: Overcoming the Anguish. International Photo Exhibitions Directorate of the Union of Soviet Societies for Friendship and Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries, Moscow, 1989 (Box Shared Tamiment 014, Folder 2)
  - Negatives and contact sheets: Meeting of Committee in Solidarity with Vietnam, Kampuchea, and Laos, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 011, Folder 9)